<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ömer Saatcioglu</title>
    <link>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ömer Saatcioglu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 21:12:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://osaatcioglu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp-CLI </title>
      <link>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/whatsapp-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 21:12:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/whatsapp-cli/</guid>
      <description>I recently developed a very simple CLI app to send WhatsApp messages directly from CLI. It was a nice experience as I learned how to use Puppeteer which is a headless Chrome with Node APIs. Also, I learned how to package and publish Node Packages.
It is not very fancy but I am using it from time to time. Check out the repo at https://github.com/osaatcioglu/whatsapp-cli</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 01:36:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>I was looking for a static site generator that can work nicely with github pages. And, I came across to Hugo
It takes a bit of time to understand the template (if you don&amp;rsquo;t know go already, I don&amp;rsquo;t) and how to publish a content. But, once you are there, the rest is quite trivial.
I have also written a small script that keeps the generated files in the master branch while the source branch has all the raw files needed by Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 01:24:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I tried to write about tech and related stuff several times in different platforms. But, life got in the way and I didn&amp;rsquo;t continue. I wonder how many times I used this typical &amp;ldquo;Hello World!&amp;rdquo; post. Yet, here I am.
Failing is OK. One can still learn along the way. So, I want to try more regardless if it fails. And while I am busy with trying, I hope that my humble experience reaches to some and it gets useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 01:24:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://osaatcioglu.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description> Compiler written in Python interpreting LISP like language
The purpose of the project is to show how to parse, interpret and evaluate the abstract syntax tree.
 A django project consumes booli.se data and list the realty prices
I created this project while I was searching for an apartment. I used this tool to get a price overview of the neighbourhood that I was looking.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>